riddle_repo = [
    {
        "question": "I don’t have eyes, but once I did see. Once I had thoughts, but now I’m white and empty. What am I?",
        "answerChoices": ["A skull", "A ghost", "A mummy", "A tombstone"],
        "answer": "A skull",
    },
    {
        "question": "I have no feet to dance, I have no eyes to see, I have no life to live or die, but yet I do all three. What am I?",
        "answerChoices": ["Wind", "Fire", "Shadow", "Time"],
        "answer": "Fire",
    },
    {
        "question": "Who makes it, has no need for it. Whoever buys it won’t use it. Who uses it, won’t care. What am I?",
        "answerChoices": ["A coffin", "A book", "A car", "A house"],
        "answer": "A coffin",
    },
    {
        "question": "I protect, I stand tall my purpose is to strike fear in all. What am I?",
        "answerChoices": ["A ghost", "A scarecrow", "A skeleton", "A zombie"],
        "answer": "A scarecrow",
    },
    {
        "question": "Poor people have it. Rich people need it. If you eat it you die. What is it?",
        "answerChoices": ["Money", "Nothing", "Food", "Love"],
        "answer": "Nothing",
    },
    {
        "question": "I’m tall when I’m young, I’m short when I’m old, and once a year, I make heavy pumpkins light. What am I?",
        "answerChoices": ["A witch", "A pumpkin", "A candle", "A bat"],
        "answer": "A candle",
    },
    {
        "question": "I always leave a trace, so you can see where I’ve been. I have some extra legs, and I make people scream. What am I?",
        "answerChoices": ["A ghost", "A snake", "A spider", "A rat"],
        "answer": "A spider",
    },
    {
        "question": "What makes skeletons strong and black cats purr with delight?",
        "answerChoices": ["Milk", "Bones", "Fish", "Blood"],
        "answer": "Milk",
    },
    {
        "question": "When is it bad luck to see a black cat?",
        "answerChoices": [
            "At night",
            "On Friday",
            "When you’re a mouse",
            "When it's raining",
        ],
        "answer": "When you’re a mouse",
    },
    {
        "question": "A man was shot in the heart. Nobody tries to save him and it doesn’t kill him. What happened?",
        "answerChoices": [
            "It was a trick",
            "He was dead",
            "He was a zombie",
            "It was fake",
        ],
        "answer": "He was already dead",
    },
    {
        "question": "The more you take, the more of me there are. What am I?",
        "answerChoices": ["Footsteps", "Words", "Stories", "Steps"],
        "answer": "Footsteps",
    },
    {
        "question": "You can hear me, feel me and know that I’m there. But you’ll never ever ever find me. What am I?",
        "answerChoices": ["Air", "The wind", "Shadow", "Darkness"],
        "answer": "The wind",
    },
    {
        "question": "Each morning, I appear to lie at your feet. All day I will follow no matter how fast you run, yet I nearly perish in the midday sun.",
        "answerChoices": ["The wind", "A shadow", "Your breath", "A ghost"],
        "answer": "A shadow",
    },
    {
        "question": "Read me or write me, I’m good for a fright. I can be spooky, but I’m best told at night. What am I?",
        "answerChoices": ["A book", "A scary story", "A journal", "A poem"],
        "answer": "A scary story",
    },
    {
        "question": "This is a common little bug that many people fear. This fear has a special name. It’s arachnophobia. What am I?",
        "answerChoices": ["A bee", "A spider", "A snake", "A wasp"],
        "answer": "A spider",
    },
    {
        "question": "You can get your jack-o’-lantern here, or you can use it to fix a hole in your pumpkin. What is it?",
        "answerChoices": ["A pumpkin patch", "A garden", "A witch's hut", "A spell"],
        "answer": "A pumpkin patch",
    },
    {
        "question": "This place has hardly any lights, but a lot of creaking floors. There are all kinds of strange noises and some random slamming doors. What is it?",
        "answerChoices": ["A haunted house", "A basement", "An attic", "A forest"],
        "answer": "A haunted house",
    },
    {
        "question": "What’s the problem with twin witches?",
        "answerChoices": [
            "They're too powerful",
            "They're always arguing",
            "You never know which witch is which",
            "They double their spells",
        ],
        "answer": "You never know which witch is which",
    },
    {
        "question": "Often used by witches to cast their spell, a slimy creature am I, and ugly as well. What am I?",
        "answerChoices": ["A newt", "A bat", "A toad", "A lizard"],
        "answer": "A toad",
    },
    {
        "question": "What is red, juicy, and delicious but could be poisonous that is offered by the wrong witch?",
        "answerChoices": [
            "A tomato",
            "Snow White’s apple",
            "A cherry",
            "A pomegranate",
        ],
        "answer": "Snow White’s apple",
    },
    {
        "question": "I’m thought to bring bad luck, I blend in the night and I’m known to mingle with witches. What am I?",
        "answerChoices": ["A bat", "A ghost", "A black cat", "A toad"],
        "answer": "A black cat",
    },
    {
        "question": "It is thanks to this item that you can sweep the floor. It’s also used by witches so they can fly and soar. What is it?",
        "answerChoices": ["A mop", "A broomstick", "A vacuum", "A duster"],
        "answer": "A broomstick",
    },
    {
        "question": "Eye of newt and toe of frog, Wool of bat? Just a spot. These are all that witches brew inside this big black pot. What is it?",
        "answerChoices": ["A kettle", "A cauldron", "A pot", "A stove"],
        "answer": "A cauldron",
    },
    {
        "question": "Oz had good ones from the north and south, and wicked ones from the east and west, but flying around on a broomstick is probably how I’m known the best. What am I?",
        "answerChoices": ["A witch", "A fairy", "A goblin", "A dragon"],
        "answer": "A witch",
    },
    {
        "question": "A group of witches are having a broomstick race. The witch in third place overtakes the witch in second place. Where is she now?",
        "answerChoices": ["First place", "Second place", "Third place", "Fourth place"],
        "answer": "Second place",
    },
    {
        "question": "What do the mummies, zombies, vampires, goblins, and witches all have in common?",
        "answerChoices": [
            "They're all spooky",
            "They're all fictional",
            "The letter 'i'",
            "They all haunt",
        ],
        "answer": "The letter 'i'",
    },
    {
        "question": "If the witch has a broom and the jack-o’lantern has a candle, then what does a vampire have?",
        "answerChoices": ["A mirror", "Garlic", "A bloodhound", "A bat"],
        "answer": "A bloodhound",
    },
    {
        "question": "I am a room in your house where you watch TV and have fun, but I’m the one room in which ghosts, ghouls, and vampires will never, ever come. What am I?",
        "answerChoices": [
            "The kitchen",
            "The bathroom",
            "The living room",
            "The attic",
        ],
        "answer": "The living room",
    },
    {
        "question": "The person who built it sold it. The person who bought it never used it. The person who used it never saw it. What is it?",
        "answerChoices": ["A bed", "A coffin", "A house", "A car"],
        "answer": "A coffin",
    },
    {
        "question": "From the head down to toes, through every living being I flow. Vampires love me but some people might faint when they see me though! What am I?",
        "answerChoices": ["Blood", "Water", "Air", "Sweat"],
        "answer": "Blood",
    },
    {
        "question": "I sleep upside down and I fly through the night. I live in dark places and I don’t have good eyesight. What am I?",
        "answerChoices": ["A ghost", "A bat", "A witch", "An owl"],
        "answer": "A bat",
    },
    {
        "question": "A cloaked man went out to get his nightly drink but died soon after because his watch stopped. What happened?",
        "answerChoices": [
            "It was poison",
            "He was caught in the sun",
            "He fell asleep",
            "He was betrayed",
        ],
        "answer": "He was caught in the sun",
    },
    {
        "question": "Ghosts and vampires will come looking for me on a dark autumn night and, with a ding and a buzz, will eagerly wait with open arms for me. What am I?",
        "answerChoices": ["A pumpkin", "Candy", "Treats", "A door"],
        "answer": "Treats",
    },
    {
        "question": "No matter what type you are, when I’m thirsty, I will come and find you no matter where you are. Who am I?",
        "answerChoices": ["A werewolf", "A vampire", "A mummy", "A ghost"],
        "answer": "A vampire",
    },
    {
        "question": "Dracula loves to draw this, as well as, put it in the bank. What is it?",
        "answerChoices": ["Blood", "Gold", "Souls", "Water"],
        "answer": "Blood",
    },
    {
        "question": "A vampire’s biggest fear, but a chef’s favorite ingredient. What is it?",
        "answerChoices": ["Onions", "Garlic", "Salt", "Pepper"],
        "answer": "Garlic",
    },
    {
        "question": "With pointed fangs I sit and wait. With piercing force, I dole out fate. Over bloodless victims, I proclaim my might. I can eternally join with a single bite. What am I?",
        "answerChoices": ["A vampire", "A stapler", "A bat", "A snake"],
        "answer": "A stapler",
    },
    {
        "question": "What kind of makeup is a ghost’s favorite to wear?",
        "answerChoices": ["Blush", "Lipstick", "Mas-scare-a", "Foundation"],
        "answer": "Mas-scare-a",
    },
    {
        "question": "You may see this hairy creature by the light of the moon. You can start running but it will likely catch you soon. You can hope for escape with the rising sun. But you have a better chance with silver bullets and a gun. What am I?",
        "answerChoices": ["A vampire", "A werewolf", "A witch", "A ghost"],
        "answer": "A werewolf",
    },
    {
        "question": "You’re in a room and there’s a ghost in the room, but you are the only one in the room. How is this possible?",
        "answerChoices": [
            "You are a mirror",
            "You are the ghost",
            "It's an illusion",
            "You're dreaming",
        ],
        "answer": "You are the ghost",
    },
    {
        "question": "Frankenstein’s father has three sons. The names of two of them are Snap and Crackle. What is the third son called?",
        "answerChoices": ["Pop", "Frank", "Dr. Frankenstein", "Frankenstein"],
        "answer": "Frankenstein",
    },
    {
        "question": "I am present, but also past. I am wrapped, but not a gift. I am named after a parent, but have no children.",
        "answerChoices": ["A mummy", "A ghost", "A vampire", "A bat"],
        "answer": "A mummy",
    },
    {
        "question": "I have a body, arms, legs and a head, but I’m heartless and have no guts. What am I?",
        "answerChoices": ["A mummy", "A skeleton", "A zombie", "A scarecrow"],
        "answer": "A skeleton",
    },
    {
        "question": "What goes “Ha, ha, ha, THUD?”",
        "answerChoices": [
            "A ghost",
            "A mummy",
            "A zombie laughing his head off",
            "A skeleton",
        ],
        "answer": "A zombie laughing his head off",
    },
    {
        "question": "Why don’t mummies take vacations?",
        "answerChoices": [
            "They can't travel",
            "They're afraid to fly",
            "They’ll unwind",
            "They don't like sun",
        ],
        "answer": "They’ll unwind",
    },
    {
        "question": "What is wicked, homeless, white and goes up and down?",
        "answerChoices": ["A bat", "A ghost in an elevator", "A witch", "A zombie"],
        "answer": "A ghost in an elevator",
    },
    {
        "question": "Day and night my bones are white. What am I?",
        "answerChoices": ["A skeleton", "A ghost", "A mummy", "A zombie"],
        "answer": "A skeleton",
    },
    {
        "question": "I am wrapped but I am not a gift, I am kept neatly in a chamber and Archeologists find me as a great treasure. What am I?",
        "answerChoices": ["A mummy", "A ghost", "A vampire", "A zombie"],
        "answer": "A mummy",
    },
    {
        "question": "I wander around, although I am dead. I like to eat the brains in your head. What am I?",
        "answerChoices": ["A ghost", "A vampire", "A zombie", "A werewolf"],
        "answer": "A zombie",
    },
    {
        "question": "Where do ghosts, mummies, and zombies love to swim?",
        "answerChoices": ["A pool", "The Dead Sea", "A swamp", "A river"],
        "answer": "The Dead Sea",
    },
    {
        "question": "What’s big, scary and has three wheels?",
        "answerChoices": [
            "A ghost car",
            "A monster riding a tricycle",
            "A haunted cart",
            "A skeleton bike",
        ],
        "answer": "A monster riding a tricycle",
    },
    {
        "question": "Pearly and white, spooky alright, playing with children every night. Who am I?",
        "answerChoices": [
            "A ghost",
            "Casper the Friendly Ghost",
            "A mummy",
            "A skeleton",
        ],
        "answer": "Casper the Friendly Ghost",
    },
    {
        "question": "Often buried with fabulous wealth an undead creature am I, all wrapped up in myself. What am I?",
        "answerChoices": ["A ghost", "A zombie", "A mummy", "A witch"],
        "answer": "A mummy",
    },
    {
        "question": "Made out of different body parts. Brought to life by electricity. Bolts in my neck and yellowish skin. Why can’t people show me some pity? Who am I?",
        "answerChoices": ["A ghost", "A zombie", "Frankenstein", "A vampire"],
        "answer": "Frankenstein",
    },
    {
        "question": "What do you call a skeleton that makes you laugh and giggle when you’re sad?",
        "answerChoices": [
            "A happy skeleton",
            "A funny bone",
            "A laughing skull",
            "A giggle ghost",
        ],
        "answer": "A funny bone",
    },
]
